Memory Books Collection MS075
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Memory Books Collection
1849 -- 1986
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Tufts College
MS075
47.57 Linear Feet 107 boxes
2 Volumes
1 Artifact(s)
Arrangement
This collection is organized into two series: Memory books and Unprocessed accessions.
Scope and Contents
This is an artificially created collection of scrapbooks, mixed photo albums, and diaries donated separately to Tufts University and compiled by alumni and faculty.
Related Materials
UA039-007 Clifford Berlin Donick Class of 1923 scrapbook
Biographical / Historical
Tufts College was founded in 1852 by a group of Universalists who had for years worked to open a non-sectarian institution of higher learning.
By 1830, Universalist efforts to build an institution of higher learning were increasing in both frequency and strength. Many Universalist ministers and laymen alike felt that their community needed a school that intertwined theological and liberal arts courses. Their opponents, however, feared the creation of a theological institution, as they felt it would create clerical domination, and prevent uneducated but devoted Universalists from becoming clergymen.
In 1835, at the annual General Convention, Thomas Jefferson Sawyer, a prominent Universalist, put forth a recommendation calling for the question of establishing a Theological Seminary to be put to the denomination at large. The resolution was adopted, and for the next four years, Sawyer's colleague, Reverend Thomas Whittemore, worked tirelessly to drum up support, both through columns in the Universalist paper, "The Trumpet," and through speeches.
By this time it had become clear that a Universalist theological college was a necessary step for the advancement of the religion. Hosea Ballou 2nd, a prolific writer and well-known minister, served as a teacher for many young Universalists interested in joining the clergy. The demand for his teaching had become so great that he had begun to teach classes instead of individual students. This high demand illustrated the need for an official school, planned for either upstate New York or the Boston, Massachusetts, area.
At the Massachusetts State Convention in 1840, attendees authorized the creation of a board of trustees to raise funds, find a site, and erect the buildings for a Universalist college. The committee included both Hosea Ballou and his son, Hosea Ballou 2nd. After the creation of the board, serious fundraising began, with a goal of $50,000 set for the campaign. Due to a lack of popular support and internal tension on the board, the first effort eventually failed.
In 1847, another fundraising drive began, this time with a goal of $100,000. Otis Skinner, another prominent Universalist, was selected to head the fundraising team. By 1851, Skinner and his team had reached the goal. By this time, the trustees had also selected the site of the future college. Earlier in the decade, Charles Tufts had donated $20,000 worth of Medford land to the trustees with the stipulation that the college be built on the site. This caused a rift among the trustees. Some felt that the college belonged in New York, others voted for Springfield, and even Hosea Ballou 2nd felt that the Tufts location was too close to Harvard and Boston. The question was put to a vote, and eventually the Medford site prevailed.
On April 22, 1852, Massachusetts granted a charter to the Trustees of Tufts College for the establishment of an institution of higher learning. The now official Trustees attempted to elect Thomas Jefferson Sawyer as the first president of Tufts, but his salary demands were too high. By 1853, Hosea Ballou 2nd had been selected as the institution's first president. By the fall of 1854, Tufts College, though not yet formally opened, had begun operation. On August 22, 1855, the college held a formal opening, and the first formal term saw over thirty students enrolled.
Tufts College continued as a liberal arts institution until the fall of 1869, when the Divinity School officially opened. In his will, benefactor Sylvanius Packard had earmarked $300,000 for Tufts, but stipulated that part of the trust must go to the establishment of a Professorship of Christian Theology. Hoping to remain a non-sectarian school, Tufts instead opted to found a separate and quasi-independent Divinity School. In 1906, the Divinity School was renamed the Crane Theological School, and continued operation until 1968.
The next major event in early Tufts history was the decision to become a co-educational institution. After ten years of debate, the Trustees finally decided to bring women to Tufts College in 1892. Although men and women originally took classes together, Tufts provided separate housing and dining facilities. By the first decade of the twentieth century, however, many administrators were becoming more and more opposed to co-education. Tufts had seen a drop in male enrollment, and many worried that it was because of the presence of women in classes. Women had also begun to dominate academically. In 1906, for example, all five seniors elected to Phi Beta Kappa were female. The co-education question was solved in 1910 using funds from an 1895 grant. Cornelia Marie Jackson had left half of her estate to Tufts to improve facilities for women, including a stipulation that a building be constructed and named The Cornelia M. Jackson College for Women. In 1910, the Trustees decided to use Jackson's funds to create a coordinate college. Jackson was to be separate from Tufts, with female only classes, dormitories, and dining halls. The Trustees felt it was the best way to improve male enrollment without alienating women. Male and female students remained segregated until 1913, when classes were again made co-educational.
Soon after Tufts became co-educational, an opportunity for a new branch of the college appeared in Boston. In 1893, seven faculty members from the College of Physicians and Surgeons, dissatisfied with their employer, left the school and with the backing of Tufts College formed the Tufts School of Medicine. The downtown Boston school soon spawned another branch. In 1899, Tufts acquired the Boston Dental College, and the renamed Tufts School of Dental Medicine began operation in close coordination with the Tufts School of Medicine.
Tufts continued its expansion into the twentieth century. In 1933, with a bequest from trustee Austin B. Fletcher, Tufts opened the Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy. The school, opened with the collaboration of Harvard University, became the first graduate school of international affairs in the United States. It also brought tremendous prestige to Tufts, which was quickly gaining a reputation as an excellent school.
Expansion continued into the 1940's, when Tufts allied with the Bouve-Boston School of Physical Therapy and Physical Education in 1942. In 1945, Tufts formed alliances with both the School of the Museum of Fine Arts and the Boston School of Occupational Therapy. In 1951, Tufts began operating the Boston Nursery Training School as a separate entity under the College of Special Studies. In 1955, the school was renamed the Eliot Pearson Children's School.
1955 brought another important change for Tufts. A petition from the Trustees dated January 20, 1955, and approved on January 28, officially changed the name of the school to Tufts University. The name change, one of President Nils Y. Wessell's original goals, was cited as both an official recognition of an already established event, and also as a recognition of a desirable direction for Tufts to move in.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Scrapbooks; Photographs; Alumni collections; University history
- Memory books, 1849 -- 1986; MS075.001; 47.57 Linear Feet; 2 Volumes; 1 Artifact(s)
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains memory books compiled by alumni and faculty of times at Tufts. Formats include scrapbooks, mixed photo albums, and diaries.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - D.G. Tomlinson, Journal, 1849; MS075.001.009.001 (Box 9)
    Private journal
    Scrapbook; Tomlinson, D.G.
  - S. Barden, Ocean Flowers, Scrapbook of pressed flowers and seaweed, 1859; MS075.001.076.001 (Volume 76)
    Pressed flowers and seaweed
    Scrapbook; Barden, S.
  - Phillip Johnson Larrabee Class of 1867 memory book, circa 1864 -- 1867; MS075.000117; 1.42 Linear Feet 1 oversize box (Box 121)
    Contains photographs of professors and classmates, and loose materials including tuition bills, photographs, poetry, a bookplate, teaching certificates, and awards. Larrabee attended Tufts from 1864-1867 and died in 1930.
    Related Materials
    Vertical File Collection, 1695 -- 2012. Tufts University. Digital Collections and Archives. Medford, MA
  - C. Ridler, Scrapbook of Alumni, 1865 -- 1915; MS075.001.011.001 (Box 11)
    Private journal.
    Scrapbook; Ridler, C.E.
  - C.E. Ridler, Scrapbook, 1871 -- 1918; MS075.001.019.001 (Box 19)
    Box 2; Newspaper clippings, programs, and misc. memorabilia.
    Ridler, C.E.
  - Tufts College Publishing Association, ledger book, 1874 -- 1908; MS075.001.109.001 (Box 109)
  - V. E. Tomlinson, newspaper clippings, 1878 -- 1938; MS075.001.063.001 (Box 63)
    Includes Edwin C. Bolles signatures and photos.
    Scrapbook
  - Mr. and Mrs. Dudley Williams, Scrapbook, 1882; MS075.001.034.001 (Box 34)
    Scrapbook of responses to 50th anniversary party invitation
    Williams, Mr. and Mrs. Dudley
  - V.E. Tomlinson, Journal, 1882; MS075.001.013.001 (Box 13)
    Tomlinson, V.E.
  - V.E. Tomlinson, Journal, 1883 -- 1986; MS075.001.026.001 (Box 26)
  - Mrs. Sol Smith, Scrapbook, 1890 -- 1910; MS075.001.020.001 (Box 20)
    Photographs, newspaper clippings, announcements, and misc. memorabilia.
    Smith, Mrs. Sol
  - Guy M. Winslow, Physics Notebook, 1891 -- 1902; MS075.001.102.001 (Box 102)
    Leaves from a physics notebook.
    Scrapbook; Winslow, Guy Monroe
  - Walter H. Belcher, Scrapbook, 1893 -- 1896; MS075.001.018.001 (Box 18)
    Newspaper clippings, announcements, and misc. memorabilia.
    Belcher, Walter H.
  - Class of 1887, Scrapbook, 1894 -- 1937; MS075.001.088.001 (Box 88)
    Newsclippings, Leo Lewis letters, 50th reunion materials, and misc. memorabilia
  - Helen Ridler White Page's Photo Album, 1895 -- 1899; MS075.001.048.001 (Box 48)
    Helen Ridler White, 1899.
  - Frank W. Lovering, scrapbook and newspaper clippings, May 23, 1897; MS075.001.057.001 (Box 57)
  - Marked-up copy of History of Tufts College from 1854 to 1896, 1897 -- 1911; MS075.001.036.001 (Box 36)
    Box 2; book contains newspaper clippings.
  - Marked-up copy of History of Tufts College from 1854 to 1896, 1897 -- 1906; MS075.001.035.001 (Box 35)
    Box 1; book contains newspaper clippings.
  - V. E. Tomlinson, book of poetry, 1897; MS075.001.064.001 (Box 64)
    Half printed, half added hand written pages.
  - Willard C. Hazelton, Scrapbook, 1897 -- 1913; MS075.001.024.001 (Box 24)
    Given by Dr. Paul K. French, Newspaper clippings and misc. memorabilia.
    Hazelton, Willard C.
  - Guy M. Winslow, Anatomy Notebook with Dr. Charles Paine Thayer, 1899 -- 1900; MS075.001.100.001 (Box 100)
    Leaves from an anatomy notebook with Dr. Charles Paine Thayer.
    Scrapbook; Winslow, Guy Monroe; Thayer, Charles Paine
  - Guy M. Winslow, Zoological Questions Notebook, 1899 -- 1902; MS075.001.101.001 (Box 101)
    Leaves from a zoological notebook.
  - Guy M. Winslow, Physiology Notebook, 1900; MS075.001.099.001 (Box 99)
    Leaves from a physiology notebook
  - Guy M. Winslow, Physiology Notebook, 1900; MS075.001.103.001 (Box 103)
    Given by Donald J. Winslow; leaves from a physiology notebook.
  - Dr. Nils Wessell, Scrapbook, 1900; MS075.001.098.001 (Box 98)
    Scrapbook given to Dr. Nil Wessell by the Marshfield Historical Society on October 20, 1965; photos.
  - Royce, Psychology Notebook, 1900; MS075.001.104.001 (Box 104)
    Leaves from a psychology notebook; author only identified as "Royce".
  - William Burnell, Scrapbook, 1900 -- 1904; MS075.001.085.001 (Box 85)
    Newsclippings, photos, fraternity memorabilia, music scores, and misc. memorabilia
    Scrapbook; Burnell, William; Zeta Psi
  - Arthur W. Coolidge, Scrapbook, 1901 -- 1902; MS075.001.016.001 (Box 16)
    Scrapbook containing newspaper clippings
    Coolidge, Arthur W.
  - Unidentified Scrapbook, 1903 -- 1908; MS075.001.021.001 (Box 21)
    Newspaper clippings, photographs, and misc. memorabilia.
  - Cedric Powers, scrapbook, 1904 -- 1909; MS075.001.053.001 (Box 53)
    Cedric Powers, E1906
  - Frederick W. Hamilton, scrapbook, 1905; MS075.001.055.001 (Box 55)
    Box 1 of 2.
  - Frederick W. Hamilton, scrapbook, 1905; MS075.001.056.001 (Box 56)
    Box 2of 2.
  - Angie M. Tripp, Scrapbook, 1906; MS075.001.005.001 (Box 5)
    Given by Mrs. Donald Madden; programs, newspaper clippings, letters, misc. memorabilia
    Scrapbook; Tripp, Angie M.
  - E.H. Clement, Universalist Scrapbook, 1906 -- 1907; MS075.001.105.001 (Box 105)
    Newspaper clippings and misc. memorabilia.
    Scrapbook; Clement, E.H.
  - Genevieve Fosdick, scrapbook, 1906 -- 1910; MS075.001.001.001 (Box 1)
  - George S. Miller, Class of 1906 Scrapbook, MS075.001.003.001 (Box 3)
    Box 2; programs, newspaper clippings, misc. memorabilia
    College presidents; Scrapbook; Miller, George Stewart; Office of the President
  - George S. Miller, Class of 1906 Scrapbook, MS075.001.004.001 (Box 4)
    Box 1; programs, newspaper clippings, misc. memorabilia
  - Nelson F. Pitts Scrapbook, 1906 -- 1911; MS075.001.033.001 (Box 33)
    Newspaper clippings, announcements, programs, and misc. memorabilia.
    Pitts, Nelson F.
  - Harry J. Burt, scrapbook, 1908 -- 1909; MS075.001.012.00002 (Box 12)
    Newspaper clippings.
  - Leroy G. Jackson, Scrapbook, 1908 -- 1912; MS075.001.083.001 (Box 83)
    Given by Paul K. Jackson; newsclippings, photos, Freshman Rules, "Votes for Wimmen," and misc. memorabilia.
    Scrapbook; Jackson, Leroy G.
  - Lucy A. Reed, Scrapbook, 1908 -- 1913; MS075.001.089.001 (Box 89)
    Letters, invitations, dance cards, and misc. memorabilia
    Scrapbook; Reed, Lucy A.
  - Russell G. Hemenway, Scrapbook, 1908 -- 1910; MS075.001.087.001 (Box 87)
    Newsclippings, photos, programs, letters, and misc. memorabilia
  - Unidentified Newsclippings, 1908 -- 1910; MS075.001.022.001 (Box 22)
    Newspaper clippings, announcements, photographs, and misc. memorabilia.
  - Harry J. Burt, scrapbook, 1909 -- 1911; MS075.001.012.00001 (Box 12)
  - Harry J. Burt, scrapbook, 1909 -- 1911; MS075.001.110.001 (Box 12)
  - Earl S. Wallace, Scrapbook, 1910; MS075.001.007.001 (Box 7)
    Memory and Fellowship Book, programs, newspaper clippings, misc. memorabilia
    Scrapbook; Wallace, Earl S.
  - Harry J. Burt, scrapbook, 1910 -- 1911; MS075.001.012.00003 (Box 12)
  - Samuel P. Ridler, Scrapbook, 1910 -- 1911; MS075.001.031.001 (Box 31)
    Scrapbook of newspaper clippings
    Ridler, Samuel P.
  - C.E. Ridler, Scrapbook, 1911 -- 1915; MS075.001.015.001 (Box 15)
    Scrapbook containing newspaper clippings.
  - Class Day scrapbook, 1911; MS075.001.059.001 (Box 59)
    Scrapbook of advice for future Class Day committees, started in 1911. Box 1 of 2.
  - Class Day scrapbook, 1911; MS075.001.060.001 (Box 60)
    Scrapbook of advice for future Class Day committees, started in 1911. Box 2 of 2.
  - Harry J. Burt, scrapbook, 1911 -- 1912; MS075.001.012.00004 (Box 12)
  - Laurence H. Teel, Scrapbook, 1911 -- 1915; MS075.001.006.001 (Box 6)
    Memory and Fellowship Book, programs, newspaper clippings, letters, misc. memorabilia
    Scrapbook; Teel, Laurence H.
  - Boston Globe articles written by Percy M. Proctor, 1912 -- 1913; MS075.001.014.001 (Box 14)
    Given by Persis Proctor Farley; journal containing newspaper clippings
    Proctor, Percy M.
  - C. Ridler, newsclippings, 1912 -- 1913; MS075.001.108.001 (Box 108)
  - C.E. Ridler, Scrapbook, 1912 -- 1914; MS075.001.023.001 (Box 23)
  - Unidentified Scrapbook of Newspaper Clippings re Music performances, 1912 -- 1914; MS075.001.107.001 (Box 107)
  - Lucy A. Reed, scrapbook, vol. 2, 1913 -- 1917; MS075.001.106.001 (Box 106)
  - Edward Andreas Terhune, Scrapbook, 1914 -- 1918; MS075.001.017.001 (Box 17)
    Photo album.
    Terhune, Edward Andreas
  - George W. Angell, Scrapbook, 1914; MS075.001.080.001 (Box 80)
    Box 1 of 2; newsclippings, photos, letters, and misc. memorabilia
    Scrapbook; Angell, George W.
  - George W. Angell, Scrapbook, 1914; MS075.001.081.001 (Box 81)
    Box 2 of 2; newsclippings, photos, letters, and misc. memorabilia
  - Isabelle Cameron, Scrapbook, 1914; MS075.001.068.001 (Box 68)
    Notes, letters, newspaper clippings, freshman button, and misc. memorabilia
    Scrapbook; Cameron, Isabelle
  - Stage photos of Jackson Gym, vol. I, 1914; MS075.001.061.00001 (Box 61)
  - Unidentified scrapbook, 1914 -- 1916; MS075.001.037.001 (Box 37)
  - C.E. Ridler, Scrapbook, 1915 -- 1916; MS075.001.030.001 (Box 30)
  - C. Ridler, Travel Scrapbook, 1915 -- 1916; MS075.001.010.001 (Box 10)
  - Photos and memorabilia, Thomas Whittemore, 1915 -- 1921; MS075.001.054.001 (Box 54)
    Includes photos of Professors Rollins and Munro, amongst others. Unable to confirm association with Thomas Whittemore. Scrapbook created after he left Tufts College.
  - Stage photos of Jackson Gym, vol. II, 1915; MS075.001.061.00002 (Box 61)
  - Unidentified scrapbook, 1915; MS075.001.032.001 (Box 32)
  - Dorothy McCoy, Scrapbook, 1916 -- 1919; MS075.001.082.001 (Box 82)
    Newsclippings, photos, letters, announcements, and misc. memorabilia.
    Scrapbook; McCoy, Dorothy
  - F. Earle Conn, A1920, 1916 -- 1921; MS075.001.113.00001 (Box 113)
    Clippings, letters, programs and photos
  - Stage photos of Jackson Gym, vol. III, 1916; MS075.001.061.00003 (Box 61)
  - Tufts Club of Boston, Constitution, Minutes, and Membership Lists, 1916 -- 1939; MS075.001.094.001 (Box 94)
    Club constitution, minutes, and membership lists
    Scrapbook; Tufts Club of Boston
  - C.E. Ridler, Scrapbook, 1917; MS075.001.029.001 (Box 29)
  - C.E. Ridler, Scrapbook, 1917 -- 1918; MS075.001.028.001 (Box 28)
  - Edith M. Doane, Scrapbook, 1917 -- 1929; MS075.001.008.001 (Box 8)
    The National Memory and Fellowship Book, programs, newspaper clippings, photographs, misc. memorabilia; begins with Camp Hohawk, 1917-1929
    Scrapbook; Doane, Edith M.
  - Lucile Kaufman, 1918 -- 1920; MS075.001.112.00001 (Box 112)
    Photo Album of Lucile Kaufman, a French exchange student to Jackson College. Includes pictures of several professors and administrators, Tufts buildings, winter activities, the Varsity Field Hockey Team of 1920 and the Jackson Class of 1920. Also includes pictures from a school dramatic group in France.
    Photographs; Buildings; Athletics
  - William C. Moodie photograph album, circa 1918 -- 1919; MS075.000120; 1 Linear Feet (Box 123)
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Gift of the family of William C. Moodie, 2021, accession MS-2021-052.
    This album was created by William C. Moodie, a member of the Class of 1919. It includes images of various campus activities, such as the Horribles Parade, bonfires, sporting events, house parties, and club activities. There are also photos of campus buildings and classmates, and many of the individuals and buildings are identified.
    Content Warning
    This album contains images of blackface on pages 12-16, and of animal dissection on page 28. For more information on DCA's content warning policy please visit our website.
  - Jason Pickford, Scrapbook, 1919; MS075.001.027.001 (Box 27)
    Scrapbook of photographs
    Pickford, Jason
  - Scrapbook, band memoranda, 1919 -- 1943; MS075.001.049.001 (Box 49)
  - Unidentified Jackson student, Scrapbook, 1919 -- 1920; MS075.001.086.002 (Box 86)
    Contains the scrapbook of an unidentified Jackson College student. The student was a member of Alpha Xi Delta. The scrapbook includes portraits of professors, photographs of campus interiors, a picture of the members of Alpha Xi Delta, and a picture of a 1920 Jackson College Baby Party.
    Scrapbook; School of Dental Medicine
  - Nickerson photo album, 1920; MS075.001.062.001 (Box 62)
    Donald E. (A20) and Carolyn Brainard (J20) Nickerson.
  - Paul J. Anderson, scrapbook, 1920; MS075.001.118.00001 (Box 118)
  - Stage photos of Jackson Gym, vol. IV, 1920; MS075.001.061.00004 (Box 61)
  - James A. Danver, Scrapbook, 1921 -- 1924; MS075.001.071.001 (Box 71)
    Scrapbook; Danver, James A.
  - John B. Belknap, scrapbook, E1928, 1922 -- 1928; MS075.001.116.00001 (Box 116)
    Donated by Bill Deuval, step-grandson of Belknap, 2008-08.
  - Marguerite H. Tracy, Jackson College Class of 1927, scrapbook, circa 1923 -- 1927; MS075.000119 (Box 119)
    Scrapbook containing a wide variety of ephemera and memorabilia, including clippings, programs, greeting cards, party favors, invitations, tickets, student regulations and other Tufts publications, and photographs. Photographs depict campus buildings, students, and traditions like "Baby Day." Notable items include a celluloid letter opener topped by an elephant figurine, a single glove, pressed flowers, a party cracker, matchbooks, Jumbo bonds, and a locket of hair. The scrapbook documents Taylor's time at Jackson College as well as her 1925 trip to France.
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    This item is fragile and requires careful handling.
    Gift of Kathryn Kibbe Manchester, May 2021, accession MS-2021-053.
  - Virginia Call, scrapbook, J1928, 1924 -- 1928; MS075.001.115.00001 (Box 115)
    Includes 5 folders of loose material removed from the back cover.
  - Genevieve Crosby, the College Girls Record Scrapbook, 1925; MS075.001.052.001 (Box 52)
    Scrapbook; Crosby, Genevieve
  - Lydia Estelle Risi J1929, scrapbook, 1925 -- 1931; MS075.001.120.00001 (Volume 120)
    This scrapbook includes photographs from Risi's time as a student of Jackson College, 1925-1929. It depicts scenes from around campus, such as the campus Reservoir (nicknamed "The Rez"), Capen House, and Goddard Chapel. There are also photographs depicting the 1926 Baby Party, the "Horribles Parade" on Junior Day circa 1928, and Risi's graduation in 1929. Also included are photographs of various vacations that Risi took in Marblehead, MA and Hampton Beach, NH. Additionally, there is a biography and an inventory of the photographs created by the donor, Risi's niece Roberta L. Walters.
    scrapbooks
  - Tufts Night at the Pops, Professor Leo Lewis, Scrapbook, 1925 -- 1939; MS075.001.069.001 (Box 69)
    Letters, programs, seating arrangements, and misc. memorabilia.
    Scrapbook; Lewis, Leo R.
  - Zero's Scrapbook published for the Old Bucks and Lame Ducks Club and The Tub, 1925 -- 1931; MS075.001.093.001 (Box 93)
    Magazines, articles, misc. memorabilia
    Scrapbook; Old Bucks & Lame Ducks Club and The Tub
  - Robert L. Nichols, Scrapbook, 1926 -- 1936; MS075.001.066.001 (Box 66)
    Box 1; newspaper clippings, photos, and misc. memorabilia.
    Scrapbook; Nichols, Robert L.
  - Robert L. Nichols, Scrapbook, 1926 -- 1936; MS075.001.067.001 (Box 67)
    Box 2; newspaper clippings, photos, and misc. memorabilia.
  - Eugen Bowen scrapbook, 1927 -- 1950; MS075.001.065.001 (Box 65)
    Photos and letters.
  - Jack Maloney, scrapbook, 1928 -- 1932; MS075.001.117.00001 (Box 117)
    Donated by Michael Parkin
    Scrapbook; Theta Delta Chi
  - Ms. Edna G. Sanford, Scrapbook, 1929 -- 1982; MS075.001.025.001 (Box 25)
    Newspaper clippings, photographs, postcards, and misc. memorabilia.
    Sanford, Edna G.
  - Tufts College Poetry Club scrapbook, 1930 -- 1932; MS075.001.058.001 (Box 58)
    Includes poetry by John Holmes.
  - Richard B. Parks scrapbook, 1933 -- 1935; MS075.000118 (Box 122)